Guide to the Reviewers Club Records, 1922-2013 RL.11303
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Reviewers Club records
1922-2013
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
Reviewers Club (Durham, N.C.)
RL.11303
4.0 Linear Feet
Records of the Reviewers Club, a women's club in Durham, N.C.
Biographical / Historical
Women's club of Durham, N.C.
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Reviewers Club Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 1975, 1992, 1997, and 2016.
Collection Overview
Records of the Reviewers Club, whose members were chiefly wives of Duke University faculty and administrators. Collection includes constitutions, standing rules, directories and rosters of members and officers, programs, minutes (1922-2010), correspondence, an article on history of the society, published in 1952, and scrapbooks containing assorted items, including clippings, photographs, and letters.
Durham (N.C.); Women -- Societies and clubs; Scrapbooks -- North Carolina -- Durham; Reviewers Club (Durham, N.C.); Duke University -- Societies, etc.
- 1975 Accession, 1922-1975; 2 boxes (Box 1-2)
- 1992-0087 Accession (Box 3)
  Scope and Contents
  Formerly Acc. 92/087: Box 1
- 1997-0064 Accession (Box 4)
  Formerly known as Acc. 97/064: Box 1
- Membership, programming, directories, 1957-1988 (Box 5)
- Scrapbook (disbound) of Reviewers Club membership, including member profiles, 1980s-1995; 2 folders (Box 5)
- Scrapbook (disbound) of Reviewers Club membership, 1997-2011; 2 folders (Box 5)
- "Celebrating 90 Years" compilation of membership, traditions, 2013 (Box 5)
- Treasurer accounts and correspondence, 1993-2003 (Box 5)
- Membership correspondence, 2013 (Box 5)
- Reviewers meeting minutes, programs/meeting materials, 1988-1997, 2000-2011; 11 folders (Box 6)